(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) SeaWorld is one of the most famous parks
in the world.
Thousands of people visit each year.
Most of them go to see the dolphins
and whales perform tricks.
This is something they could never see in
the wild.
SeaWorld has been under a lot of pressure
lately.
Thousands of people have been protesting the parks.
These people say that dolphins and whales should
not be forced to live in such small
places.
They should also never be forced to perform
pointless tricks.
Most people are starting to agree with this.
SeaWorld will hopefully start listening to the protesters
soon.